export const QuizMarvel = [
  {
    fournisseur: "Donkey Geek (https://www.youtube.com/c/DonkeyGeek)",
    sujet: "Application Marvel Quiz pour apprentissage React JS",
    quizz: {
      beginner: [
        {
          id: 0,
          question: "What team is Iceman on?",
          options: [
            "The X-Men",
            "The Fantastic Four",
            "The Invaders",
            "The Liberators",
          ],
          answer: "The X-Men",
          heroId: 1009362,
        },
        {
          id: 1,
          question: "In X-Men, what substance forms the Wolverine skeleton?",
          options: ["Cavorite", "Vibranium", "Adamantium", "Neutronium"],
          answer: "Adamantium",
          heroId: 1009718,
        },
        {
          id: 2,
          question:
            "What is the name of Spider-Man, who first appeared in 1962?",
          options: ["Tom Parker", "John Parker", "Peter Parker", "Alan Parker"],
          answer: "Peter Parker",
          heroId: 1009610,
        },
        {
          id: 3,
          question:
            "What was Wolverine's name when he was a knight of the Apocalypse?",
          options: ["Rage", "Death", "Destruction", "Oblivion"],
          answer: "Death",
          heroId: 1009718,
        },
        {
          id: 4,
          question:
            "What superhero never separates from his hammer forged by dwarves?",
          options: ["Bizarro", "Flash", "Venom", "Thor"],
          answer: "Thor",
          heroId: 1009664,
        },
        {
          id: 5,
          question: "What color is associated with Hulk?",
          options: ["Yellow", "Red", "Green", "Blue"],
          answer: "Green",
          heroId: 1009351,
        },
        {
          id: 6,
          question: "What superhero looks like a creature of stone?",
          options: ["Plastic Man", "The Thing", "Hawkman", "Superboy"],
          answer: "The Thing",
          heroId: 1009662,
        },
        {
          id: 7,
          question: "Whose butler is Edwin Jarvis?",
          options: [
            "Bruce Wayne",
            "Charles Xavier",
            "Tony Stark",
            "Henry Steven",
          ],
          answer: "Tony Stark",
          heroId: 1009368,
        },
        {
          id: 8,
          question:
            "What superhero wears a costume inspired by the American flag?",
          options: ["Tigra", "Blade", "Iron Man", "Captain America"],
          answer: "Captain America",
          heroId: 1009220,
        },
        {
          id: 9,
          question:
            "Including his thumbs, how many fingers on both hands does The Thing have?",
          options: [8, 6, 10, 4],
          answer: 8,
          heroId: 1009662,
        },
      ],
      confirmed: [
        {
          id: 0,
          question: "Who is Logan in the Marvel Comics 'X-Men' comic book?",
          options: ["Cyclope", "Colossus", "Wolverine", "Caliban"],
          answer: "Wolverine",
          heroId: 1009718,
        },
        {
          id: 1,
          question: "What superhero is interested in Sue Storm?",
          options: ["X-Men", "Illuminati", "Spider-Man", "Namor"],
          answer: "Namor",
          heroId: 1009466,
        },
        {
          id: 2,
          question: "What human becomes superpowered by high-tech armor?",
          options: ["Cyclope", "Iron Man", "Wolverine", "Thor"],
          answer: "Iron Man",
          heroId: 1009368,
        },
        {
          id: 3,
          question:
            "Which one of the proposals refers to an emblematic enemy of Spider-Man?",
          options: ["Lizard", "Thanos", "Void", "Green Goblin"],
          answer: "Green Goblin",
          heroId: 1014985,
        },
        {
          id: 4,
          question: "GHOST RIDER is known as...",
          options: [
            "The biker devil",
            "The spirit of hate",
            "The spirit of vengeance",
            "The red skull",
          ],
          answer: "The spirit of vengeance",
          heroId: 1009318,
        },
        {
          id: 5,
          question: "Before becoming Radioactive Man, Chen Lu was...",
          options: ["A spy", "A nuclear physicist", "A soldier", "A pilot"],
          answer: "A nuclear physicist",
          heroId: 1009526,
        },
        {
          id: 6,
          question:
            "What superhero with blindness has developed sensory organs?",
          options: ["Daredevil", "Flash", "Superman", "Captain America"],
          answer: "Daredevil",
          heroId: 1009262,
        },
        {
          id: 7,
          question: "Before he turned to a life of crime, Mysterio was...",
          options: [
            "Stuntman",
            "Special effects artist",
            "Magician",
            "Fireman",
          ],
          answer: "Special effects artist",
          heroId: 1010952,
        },
        {
          id: 8,
          question: "Fin Fang Foom is an alien from...",
          options: ["Krypton", "Maklu IV", "Mars", "Vulcan"],
          answer: "Maklu IV",
          heroId: 1009303,
        },
        {
          id: 9,
          question: "DOCTOR DOOM studied at the same college as...",
          options: [
            "Tony Stark",
            "Peter Parker",
            "Reed Richards",
            "Bruce Banner",
          ],
          answer: "Reed Richards",
          heroId: 1009281,
        },
      ],
      expert: [
        {
          id: 0,
          question:
            "When she worked for Hydra, Spider-Woman's first mission was to...",
          options: [
            "Seduce Iron-Man",
            "Seduce Spider-Man",
            "Kill The Black Widow",
            "Kill Nick Fury",
          ],
          answer: "Kill Nick Fury",
          heroId: 1009608,
        },
        {
          id: 1,
          question:
            "Which superhero created by Marvel Comics is blind from birth?",
          options: ["Flash", "Thor", "Cyclope", "Stick"],
          answer: "Stick",
          heroId: 1009626,
        },
        {
          id: 2,
          question:
            "Spider-Man was asked to create the Spider-Mobile by the advertising company of...",
          options: [
            "Carter Lombardo",
            "Max Shrek",
            "Reed Richards",
            "Spider Company",
          ],
          answer: "Carter Lombardo",
          heroId: 1009610,
        },
        {
          id: 3,
          question: "What Daredevil heroine is a professional killer?",
          options: ["Ultron", "Catwoman", "Elektra", "Wonder Woman"],
          answer: "Elektra",
          heroId: 1009288,
        },
        {
          id: 4,
          question:
            "Where lives Mandarin who recently became the boss of Sin-Cong Wong Chu?",
          options: [
            "The Valley of Spirits",
            "The Mountains of Asgard",
            "The Canyons of Atlantis",
            "The Cave of Souls",
          ],
          answer: "The Valley of Spirits",
          heroId: 1009421,
        },
        {
          id: 5,
          question: "What superhero has the same powers as Spider-Man?",
          options: ["Venom", "Green Arrow", "Blade", "Bizarro"],
          answer: "Venom",
          heroId: 1010788,
        },
        {
          id: 6,
          question: "Nick Fury has a brother who's gone evil. What's his name?",
          options: ["Venom", "Viper", "The Red Skull", "Scorpio"],
          answer: "Scorpio",
          heroId: 1011007,
        },
        {
          id: 7,
          question: "Miss Marvel has never been known as...",
          options: ["Captain Marvel", "Rogue", "Warbird", "Binary"],
          answer: "Rogue",
          heroId: 1010338,
        },
        {
          id: 8,
          question: "Who is Dr. Strange's close heroine created in 1964?",
          options: ["Felina", "Clea", "Monica", "Elsa"],
          answer: "Clea",
          heroId: 1009239,
        },
        {
          id: 9,
          question: "As a child, Storm tried to...",
          options: [
            "Burning down a village with a thunderbolt",
            "Becoming the leader of a gang",
            "Steal Professor Xavier's car",
            "Picking Professor Xavier's pockets",
          ],
          answer: "Picking Professor Xavier's pockets",
          heroId: 1009629,
        },
      ],
    },
  },
];
